[
  {
    "id": 0,
    "name": "Pierre",
    "cardType": "ROOMMATE",
    "neededDice": [
      {
        "number": "1",
        "count": 2
      }
    ],
    "cardFront": "normal_pierre_vs",
    "cardBack": "normal_pierre_rs"
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "name": "Anita",
    "cardType": "ROOMMATE",
    "neededDice": [
      {
        "number": "3",
        "count": 2
      }
    ],
    "cardFront": "normal_anita_vs",
    "cardBack": "normal_anita_rs"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "name": "Anneliese",
    "cardType": "ROOMMATE",
    "neededDice": [
      {
        "number": "3",
        "count": 2
      }
    ],
    "cardFront": "normal_anneliese_vs",
    "cardBack": "normal_anneliese_rs"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "name": "Astrid",
    "cardType": "ROOMMATE",
    "neededDice": [
      {
        "number": "4",
        "count": 2
      }
    ],
    "cardFront": "normal_astrid_vs",
    "cardBack": "normal_astrid_rs"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "name": "Bärbel",
    "cardType": "ROOMMATE",
    "neededDice": [
      {
        "number": "1",
        "count": 2
      }
    ],
    "cardFront": "normal_bärbel_vs",
    "cardBack": "normal_bärbel_rs"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "name": "Carsten",
    "cardType": "ROOMMATE",
    "neededDice": [
      {
        "number": "5",
        "count": 2
      }
    ],
    "cardFront": "normal_carsten_vs",
    "cardBack": "normal_carsten_rs"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "name": "Didi Kötke",
    "cardType": "ROOMMATE",
    "neededDice": [
      {
        "number": "5",
        "count": 2
      }
    ],
    "cardFront": "normal_didi_vs",
    "cardBack": "normal_didi_rs"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "name": "Ekkehard",
    "cardType": "ROOMMATE",
    "neededDice": [
      {
        "number": "2",
        "count": 2
      }
    ],
    "cardFront": "normal_ekkehard_vs",
    "cardBack": "normal_ekkehard_rs"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "name": "Jennifer",
    "cardType": "ROOMMATE",
    "neededDice": [
      {
        "number": "5",
        "count": 2
      }
    ],
    "cardFront": "normal_jennifer_vs",
    "cardBack": "normal_jennifer_rs"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "name": "Jesus",
    "cardType": "ROOMMATE",
    "neededDice": [
      {
        "number": "3",
        "count": 2
      }
    ],
    "cardFront": "normal_jesus_vs",
    "cardBack": "normal_jesus_rs"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "name": "Johannes",
    "cardType": "ROOMMATE",
    "neededDice": [
      {
        "number": "4",
        "count": 2
      }
    ],
    "cardFront": "normal_johannes_vs",
    "cardBack": "normal_johannes_rs"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "name": "Julia",
    "cardType": "ROOMMATE",
    "neededDice": [
      {
        "number": "2",
        "count": 2
      }
    ],
    "cardFront": "normal_julia_vs",
    "cardBack": "normal_julia_rs"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "name": "Manni",
    "cardType": "ROOMMATE",
    "neededDice": [
      {
        "number": "2",
        "count": 2
      }
    ],
    "cardFront": "normal_manni_vs",
    "cardBack": "normal_manni_rs"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "name": "Maria-Theresia",
    "cardType": "ROOMMATE",
    "neededDice": [
      {
        "number": "5",
        "count": 2
      }
    ],
    "cardFront": "normal_mariatheresia_vs",
    "cardBack": "normal_mariatheresia_rs"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "name": "Paula",
    "cardType": "ROOMMATE",
    "neededDice": [
      {
        "number": "4",
        "count": 2
      }
    ],
    "cardFront": "normal_paula_vs",
    "cardBack": "normal_paula_rs"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "name": "Sissi",
    "cardType": "ROOMMATE",
    "neededDice": [
      {
        "number": "4",
        "count": 2
      }
    ],
    "cardFront": "normal_sissi_vs",
    "cardBack": "normal_sissi_rs"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "name": "Alex",
    "cardType": "ROOMMATE",
    "neededDice": [
      {
        "number": "1",
        "count": 2
      }
    ],
    "cardFront": "normal_alex_vs",
    "cardBack": "normal_alex_rs"
  }
]